

CONTACT ME AT

- Jl. Jend. Sudirman,
 Biringere, Sinjai Utara,
 Sinjai, South Sulawesi
- kalamangna@gmail.com
- github.com/kalamangna
- in linkedin.com/in/kalamangna
- kalamangna.github.io

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Vue.js
- Javascript
- Nuxt.js
- Responsive Web
- React.js
- Bootstrap
- HTML
- Vuetify
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- SCSS
- Material UI

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Universitas Gadjah Mada

Bachelor of Engineering Information Technology 2014 - 2019

• GPA 2,78

SMA Negeri 1 Sinjai

ABD DZULJALALI WAL IKRAM

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Hello! You can call me Abed. I'm a detail oriented Frontend Developer based in South Sulawesi, Indonesia. With more than 1 year professional experience in website development, I have acquired the skills necessary to build great websites.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer - Frontend

PT. Pialang Asuransi Provis Mitra Sinergi | Dec 2020 - Present

• Developed internal website as content management system using React.js, Material UI, and Redux.

Frontend Developer (Freelance)

Fairtech Pte Ltd | Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

- Developed landing page using HTML, CSS, and SCSS as user platform to view and order diving spot in Indonesia.
- Implemented Gulp.js for minifying CSS and Javascript files before deployment to server.

Frontend Engineer

PT. Bayanaka Destina Nusantara | Nov 2019 - Nov 2020

- Developed landing page using Nuxt.js (Vue.js framework) as user platform to order tour packages.
- Modified content management system as admin platform to input data that saved to database.
- Applied UI design into website interface including responsive design using Vuetify (UI framework).
- Implemented Vuex as global state management to store defined data so that it can be used by all components.

Software Engineer (Internship)

PT. Telekomunikasi Indonesia | Jan 2018 - Feb 2018

 Developed information system using Vanilla.js to help employees in managing incoming and outgoing devices so it can be monitored by manager.